{
    "id": "588b93667b034b11bbae9af7a2290b62",
    "title": "Second Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Everything ..................... she said is true.",
            "description": "That is common after expressions like all, everything, anything, nothing, few etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody was there ............................ James.",
            "description": "Except and except for are possible after words like all, every, no, anybody etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "except",
                "except for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... your help, I would have failed.",
            "description": "Without and but for are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "Without",
                "But",
                "But for",
                "Except"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been like that ...................... her childhood.",
            "description": "We prefer since here however, from is also possible. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... us has been invited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "None of",
                "None",
                "No one"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... what you think.",
            "description": "No matter is a conjunction. It doesn't matter is an expression used to introduce a sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "It doesn't matter",
                "No matter"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is fourth cake you ................................ this morning.",
            "description": "We use a present perfect tense with 'this is the first / second / third / last etc.'",
            "answers": [
                "ate",
                "have eaten",
                "are eating"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t come today. I would rather you .............................. tomorrow.",
            "description": "After would rather, we use a past tense to refer to present or future,",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "came",
                "have come"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had gone to university, I .............................. business administration.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "will study",
                "would study",
                "would have studied"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Nine o’clock. It is time you ....................... home.",
            "description": "After it's time, we use a past tense with present meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ........................... the man from head to foot.",
            "description": "To search for is to look for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "searched",
                "searched for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I wasn’t pleased ................................ my exam results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "about",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        }
    ]
}